<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>Yalla Video Manual PAD</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>PAD file follows the PAD 4.0 specification. See http://pad.asp-software.org for details. This PAD describes the macOS (Apple Silicon) installer; see pad_file_windows.xml and pad_file_linux.xml for other platforms.</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>

  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>Monzer Osman</Company_Name>
    <Address_1></Address_1>
    <Address_2></Address_2>
    <City_Town></City_Town>
    <State_Province></State_Province>
    <Zip_Postal_Code></Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Country></Country>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>https://github.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Author_First_Name>Monzer</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Osman</Author_Last_Name>
      <Author_Email>monzerosman15@gmail.com</Author_Email>
      <Contact_First_Name>Monzer</Contact_First_Name>
      <Contact_Last_Name>Osman</Contact_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>monzerosman15@gmail.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
    <Support_Info>
      <Sales_Email>monzerosman15@gmail.com</Sales_Email>
      <Support_Email>monzerosman15@gmail.com</Support_Email>
      <General_Email>monzerosman15@gmail.com</General_Email>
      <Sales_Phone></Sales_Phone>
      <Support_Phone></Support_Phone>
      <General_Phone></General_Phone>
      <Fax_Phone></Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
  </Company_Info>

  <Program_Info>
    <Program_Name>Yalla Video</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>1.1.2</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>05</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>15</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2026</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>0.00</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code>USD</Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other></Program_Cost_Other>
    <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>Minor Update</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>macOS 11,macOS 12,macOS 13,macOS 14,macOS 15</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English,Arabic,Spanish,French,German,Italian,Portuguese,Russian,Turkish,Chinese,Japanese,Korean</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>Renamed application identifier for Flathub compatibility. No functional changes.</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_Specific_Category>Audio &amp; Video</Program_Specific_Category>
    <Program_Category_Class>Audio &amp; Video::Video Tools</Program_Category_Class>
    <Program_System_Requirements>macOS 11 Big Sur or later, Apple Silicon (M1/M2/M3/M4). Internet connection required for downloads. ~400 MB free disk space.</Program_System_Requirements>
  </Program_Info>

  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Keywords>video downloader, YouTube downloader, playlist downloader, 4K, 8K, MP4, MP3, subtitles, yt-dlp, ffmpeg, batch download, audio extractor, video converter, channel downloader, privacy</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Fast YouTube &amp; 1000+ sites video downloader.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Privacy-first desktop downloader for YouTube and 1000+ sites, up to 8K.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Yalla Video is a fast, privacy-first desktop app to download videos from YouTube and 1000+ sites. Grab single videos, playlists, or entire channels with bulk selection. Choose any quality up to 8K, audio-only formats, and multi-language subtitles.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Yalla Video is a fast, privacy-first desktop downloader for YouTube and 1000+ sites. Download single videos, full playlists, or entire channels with filters, search, and bulk selection. Pick any quality up to 8K, choose video or audio-only formats (MP4, MKV, MP3, M4A, WAV), and grab multi-language subtitles. Features parallel downloads, bandwidth limits, scheduling, pause/resume, proxy support, and a clipboard tray. No setup required.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Yalla Video is a fast, privacy-first desktop downloader for YouTube and 1000+ other sites. Grab single videos, full playlists, or entire channels in one go — with filters, search, and bulk selection. Pick any quality up to 8K, choose video or audio-only formats (MP4, MKV, MP3, M4A, WAV, and more), and download multi-language subtitles (embedded or sidecar SRT/VTT). Smart Mode picks the best format automatically; manual mode gives full control over codec, frame rate, and resolution. Features parallel downloads with bandwidth limits, schedule-for-later, auto-retry, pause/resume, batch URL paste, proxy/SOCKS support, browser cookie import, and a clipboard-aware tray for one-click captures. yt-dlp and ffmpeg install and update themselves in the background — no setup required. Available in 12 languages with light, dark, and themed UIs. Cross-platform: Windows, macOS, and Linux. Open license, no telemetry, no account required.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </English>
    <Arabic>
      <Keywords>تنزيل فيديو, تنزيل يوتيوب, قوائم التشغيل, 4K, 8K, MP4, MP3, ترجمات, تحميل مجمع, مستخرج صوت, تنزيل قنوات, خصوصية</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>تنزيل فيديوهات يوتيوب وأكثر من 1000 موقع.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>تطبيق سطح مكتب لتنزيل الفيديوهات من يوتيوب و1000+ موقع بدقة تصل إلى 8K.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>ياللا فيديو تطبيق سطح مكتب سريع يركّز على الخصوصية لتنزيل الفيديوهات من يوتيوب وأكثر من 1000 موقع. حمّل فيديوهات مفردة أو قوائم تشغيل أو قنوات كاملة. اختر أي جودة حتى 8K وصيغ الصوت فقط وترجمات بلغات متعددة.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>ياللا فيديو تطبيق سطح مكتب سريع يحترم الخصوصية لتنزيل الفيديوهات من يوتيوب وأكثر من 1000 موقع. حمّل فيديوهات مفردة، أو قوائم تشغيل كاملة، أو قنوات بأكملها مع التصفية والبحث والاختيار الجماعي. اختر أي جودة حتى 8K، صيغ فيديو أو صوت فقط (MP4, MKV, MP3, M4A, WAV)، وترجمات بلغات متعددة. ميزات: تنزيلات متوازية، حدود للنطاق الترددي، جدولة، إيقاف/استئناف، دعم البروكسي. بدون أي إعداد.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>ياللا فيديو تطبيق سطح مكتب سريع يحترم الخصوصية لتنزيل الفيديوهات من يوتيوب وأكثر من 1000 موقع آخر. حمّل فيديوهات مفردة، أو قوائم تشغيل كاملة، أو قنوات بأكملها دفعة واحدة — مع التصفية والبحث والاختيار الجماعي. اختر أي جودة حتى 8K، صيغ فيديو أو صوت فقط (MP4, MKV, MP3, M4A, WAV، والمزيد)، وترجمات بلغات متعددة (مدمجة أو ملفات SRT/VTT منفصلة). يختار الوضع الذكي أفضل صيغة تلقائياً، بينما يمنحك الوضع اليدوي تحكماً كاملاً في الكوديك ومعدل الإطارات والدقة. مميزات إضافية: تنزيلات متوازية مع حدود للنطاق الترددي، جدولة لاحقة، إعادة محاولة تلقائية، إيقاف/استئناف، لصق روابط مجمعة، دعم بروكسي/SOCKS، استيراد كوكيز المتصفح، وعلبة حافظة ذكية لالتقاط الروابط بنقرة واحدة. يقوم yt-dlp وffmpeg بالتثبيت والتحديث تلقائياً في الخلفية — لا حاجة للإعداد. متوفر بـ12 لغة مع واجهات فاتحة وداكنة وملوّنة. متعدد المنصات: Windows وmacOS وLinux. ترخيص مفتوح، بدون تتبع، بدون حساب.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </Arabic>
    <Spanish>
      <Keywords>descargador de video, descargador de YouTube, descargador de listas, 4K, 8K, MP4, MP3, subtítulos, descarga por lotes, extractor de audio, descargador de canales, privacidad</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Descargador de YouTube y 1000+ sitios.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Descargador de escritorio para YouTube y 1000+ sitios, hasta 8K, privado.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Yalla Video: app de escritorio rápida y privada para descargar videos de YouTube y 1000+ sitios. Videos sueltos, listas o canales enteros con selección múltiple. Calidad hasta 8K, audio y subtítulos en varios idiomas.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Yalla Video es un descargador de escritorio rápido y enfocado en la privacidad para YouTube y más de 1000 sitios. Descarga videos individuales, listas completas o canales enteros con filtros, búsqueda y selección múltiple. Calidad hasta 8K, video o solo audio (MP4, MKV, MP3, M4A, WAV) y subtítulos multilenguaje. Descargas paralelas, límite de ancho de banda, programación, pausa/reanudación y soporte proxy. Sin configuración.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Yalla Video es un descargador de escritorio rápido y enfocado en la privacidad para YouTube y más de 1000 sitios. Descarga videos individuales, listas de reproducción completas o canales enteros de una sola vez, con filtros, búsqueda y selección múltiple. Elige cualquier calidad hasta 8K, formatos de video o solo audio (MP4, MKV, MP3, M4A, WAV y más) y subtítulos en varios idiomas (incrustados o como archivos SRT/VTT). El Modo Inteligente elige el mejor formato automáticamente; el modo manual te da control total sobre el códec, la tasa de fotogramas y la resolución. Incluye descargas paralelas con límites de ancho de banda, programación para más tarde, reintentos automáticos, pausa/reanudación, pegado masivo de URLs, soporte de proxy/SOCKS, importación de cookies del navegador y una bandeja inteligente que detecta el portapapeles para capturar enlaces con un clic. yt-dlp y ffmpeg se instalan y actualizan solos en segundo plano — no requiere configuración. Disponible en 12 idiomas con interfaces clara, oscura y temáticas. Multiplataforma: Windows, macOS y Linux. Licencia abierta, sin telemetría, sin cuenta requerida.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </Spanish>
    <French>
      <Keywords>téléchargeur vidéo, téléchargeur YouTube, téléchargeur playlist, 4K, 8K, MP4, MP3, sous-titres, téléchargement par lots, extracteur audio, téléchargeur de chaîne, confidentialité</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Téléchargeur YouTube et 1000+ sites.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Téléchargeur de bureau pour YouTube et 1000+ sites, jusqu'à 8K, privé.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Yalla Video : application de bureau rapide et privée pour télécharger des vidéos depuis YouTube et plus de 1000 sites. Vidéos seules, playlists ou chaînes entières. Qualité jusqu'en 8K, audio et sous-titres multilingues.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Yalla Video : téléchargeur de bureau rapide et privé pour YouTube et plus de 1000 sites. Téléchargez des vidéos, playlists complètes ou chaînes entières avec filtres, recherche et sélection groupée. Qualité jusqu'à 8K, vidéo ou audio uniquement (MP4, MKV, MP3, M4A, WAV) et sous-titres multilingues. Téléchargements parallèles, limite de bande passante, planification, pause/reprise, proxy. Sans configuration.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Yalla Video est un téléchargeur de bureau rapide et respectueux de la vie privée pour YouTube et plus de 1000 sites. Téléchargez des vidéos individuelles, des playlists complètes ou des chaînes entières d'un seul coup, avec filtres, recherche et sélection groupée. Choisissez n'importe quelle qualité jusqu'en 8K, des formats vidéo ou audio uniquement (MP4, MKV, MP3, M4A, WAV et plus) et des sous-titres multilingues (intégrés ou en fichiers SRT/VTT). Le Mode Intelligent choisit automatiquement le meilleur format ; le mode manuel offre un contrôle total sur le codec, la fréquence d'images et la résolution. Fonctions : téléchargements parallèles avec limites de bande passante, planification, nouvelle tentative automatique, pause/reprise, collage groupé d'URLs, support proxy/SOCKS, import de cookies du navigateur et barre d'état intelligente qui détecte le presse-papiers pour capturer un lien en un clic. yt-dlp et ffmpeg s'installent et se mettent à jour seuls en arrière-plan — aucune configuration requise. Disponible en 12 langues avec des interfaces claire, sombre et thématiques. Multiplateforme : Windows, macOS et Linux. Licence ouverte, sans télémétrie, sans compte.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </French>
  </Program_Descriptions>

  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>https://github.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>https://github.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/releases/latest/download/Yalla-Video-1.1.2-arm64.dmg</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/screenshots/home.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/icon.png</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/pad_file_macos.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
      <!--
        Additional screenshots:
          https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/screenshots/home.png
          https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/screenshots/downloads.png
          https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/screenshots/channels.png
          https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/screenshots/settings.png
          https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/screenshots/account.png
          https://raw.githubusercontent.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/master/screenshots/about.png
      -->
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>https://github.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/releases/download/v1.1.2/Yalla-Video-1.1.2-arm64.dmg</Primary_Download_URL>
      <Secondary_Download_URL>https://github.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/releases/latest/download/Yalla-Video-1.1.2-arm64.dmg</Secondary_Download_URL>
      <Additional_Download_URL_1>https://github.com/monzer15/yalla-video-releases/releases/download/v1.1.2/Yalla-Video-1.1.2-arm64-mac.zip</Additional_Download_URL_1>
      <Additional_Download_URL_2></Additional_Download_URL_2>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>

  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>Yalla Video is licensed under the MIT License. The unmodified installer may be freely distributed, mirrored, and bundled with reviews on download archive sites. Redistribution must retain the original copyright notice and license text. Modified builds must use a different product name.</Distribution_Permissions>
    <EULA>MIT License

Copyright (c) 2026 Monzer Osman

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.</EULA>
  </Permissions>

  <Program_Info_Ext>
    <File_Info>
      <File_Size_Bytes>144307173</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>140925</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>138</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Count></Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Based_On></Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Other_Info></Expire_Other_Info>
      <Expire_Month></Expire_Month>
      <Expire_Day></Expire_Day>
      <Expire_Year></Expire_Year>
    </Expire_Info>
  </Program_Info_Ext>

  <Affiliates>
    <Affiliates_Description></Affiliates_Description>
    <Affiliates_URL></Affiliates_URL>
    <Affiliates_Vendor_List></Affiliates_Vendor_List>
  </Affiliates>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
